<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Know Your Campus</string>
    <string name="main_title">Welcome to <b>Know Your Campus</b>:\nCSUN\'s official map trivia game!</string>
    <string name="main_description">Press <i>Rules</i> if this is your first time.\nPress <i>Play</i> to start the
        game.\nPress <i>Submit</i> to send scores to the leaderboard.</string>
    <string name="main_copyright">&#169; 2015 Comp 680 Team 2\n&#169; 2015 App Jam Team 12</string>
    <string name="rules_title">Rules</string>
    <string name="rules_text">In this game, players are presented with a randomized set of descriptive questions about
        the buildings on CSUN\'s campus. The goal is to answer all the questions correctly as fast as possible.\n\n
        After pressing the <i>Play</i> button, players will be presented with a map of CSUN and a question below it.
        They must scroll the map until they find the building they think answers the question best. Players must then
        \"long press\" the building on the map.\n\n
        If their answer is correct, a green border will surround their building of choice. If their answer is incorrect,
        the correct building will be displayed, with a red border surrounding it. After submitting their answer, an
        informative piece of trivia regarding CSUN will appear where the question previously was.\n\n
        Correct answers will also be awarded with an increment to the game\'s score. This increment is determined by
        two factors: the difficulty of the question (easy, medium or hard), as well as the milliseconds the player had
        remaining prior to answering it.\n\n
        When the player is ready to continue, they then press the \"Next Question\" button at the top of the screen.
        This cycle then repeats itself for all of the game questions until the last one is answered, and at this point
        it\'s <i>Game Over</i>.\n\n
        At the end of the game, the player\'s score can be sent to a leaderboard, where they can see how they rank up
        against other players. Given the variability of the score, this will incentivize the player to continue playing
        in order to get the highest score, and in the process, increasing their knowledge of CSUN\'s history and
        locations.\n\n
        In order to avoid cheating however, games are reset whenever the application is paused or exited for any
        reason.\n\n
        So, think YOU got what it takes to\n
        <i>Know Your Campus</i>?</string>
    <string name="play_title">Play</string>
    <string name="time_text">Time: 20</string>
    <string name="score_text">Score: 0</string>
    <string name="trivia_text">Where is my question?!</string>
    <string name="next_question_button">Next Question</string>
    <string name="back_submit_button">Back + Submit Score</string>
    <string name="submit_title">Submit</string>
    <string name="submit_description">---</string>
    <string name="submit_send_button">Send</string>
    <string name="submit_leaderboard_button">Leaderboard</string>
    <string name="credits_title">Credits</string>
    <string name="credits_description">Know Your Campus is an\n
        Android game application created at\n
        California State University Northridge\n
        as a project for Professor M. Boctor\'s\n
        Spring 2015 <i>Comp 680</i> class, as well as\n
        the Spring 2015 <i>App Jam</i> competition.\n
        For the former, we are <i>Team 2</i>, for the\n
        latter, we are <i>Team 12</i>.\n\n
        Our team consists of:\n
        <b>Chris Bowles\n
        Victor Perez\n
        Russell Templet\n
        Nishika Malhotra\n
        Maria Regina Velasquez\n</b>\n
        Our website can be accessed by clicking the button below, which will exit this application and open your web
        browser at our address.</string>
    <string name="credits_website_button">www.nullroute.cc</string>
    <string name="references_title">References</string>
    <string name="references_text">
        This is where the references will go.
    </string>
    <string name="device_not_supported">Google Play Services APK not supported</string>
</resources>